(Raj:)Well, it's a lot better than
(Raj:)having to wear noise-cancelling
headphones in my own apartment.
(Penny:)What? Oh, God, yeah. Yeah.
(Penny:)Leonard's a noisy little dude
in the sack.
(Raj:)Every night.
Really?
(Penny:)Even during allergy season,
when he has to alternate
(Penny:)between kissing and breathing?
(Raj:)It's my sister. Can we not
talk about this anymore?
(Penny:)Yeah. Sorry, sorry.
(Penny:)Can I tell you a secret?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)I screwed up.
(Penny:)Leonard's a great guy.
(Penny:)Never should have
broken up with him.
(Raj:)Well, uh, to paraphrase Shakespeare
"It's better to have
loved and lost
"than to stay home every night
and download
(Raj:)increasingly shameful
pornography."
Ohh... you poor baby.
(Raj:)What's wrong with me, Penny?
(Penny:)Nothing, nothing.
(Penny:)You know, if we weren't friends,
(Penny:)and you hadn't brought up
that creepy pornography story,
(Penny:)I'd be on you like
(Penny:)the speed of light squared
on matter to make energy.